OBJECTIVE

Lucky is an Electrical Engineer with 8+ years of pre and post educational, apprentice, and professional experience working with electrical designs and installation both domestic, private and industrial sector. Primarily focused on implementation of electrical designs, installations and maintenance. Excellent interpersonal and communication abilities, and possess a wide range of technical skills. Enjoys being part of a team, as well as managing, motivating and training a productive team, and thrives in high pressure and challenging working environments

EXPERIENCE

MECHANICAL/AUTOMATION MAINTENANCE TRAINEE (MECHATRONICS)

| NOV 2018 - PRESENT

Nigerian breweries plc.

- Currently undergoing training on the combined field of mechanical and automation maintenance.
- Electrical standards and practice.
- Instrumentation (pneumatics, electro pneumatics, process auto and industrial hydraulics).
- Plc serv 1&2
- Frequency drives
- Maintenance technology etc.

ELECTRICAL ENGINEER

| SEPT 2018 - PRESENT

Nel-holdman Nigeria limited.

- In charge of the company bidding process for both federal government/private contracts i.e. from bid preparations to submission.
- Prepare technical documents for assorted contracts i.e. federal/private and sub-contracts. Making sure we meet all necessary requirements for the contract qualification process.
- ightarrow Prepare electrical related BOQ/BEME for several contracts.
- Sourced for constructions materials and equipment, and negotiated prices with suppliers.
- Performed detailed calculations and formatted BOQ/BEME documents using MICROSOFT EXCELL/WORDS.
- > Design and Implement Electrical System by studying client requirement.

CONTACT

Current Home: Road 23, no1 Bashorun estate lagele, ibadan,

Oyo state.

Email: izekor.lo@gmail.com

Phone: 07038623591

SKILLS

Design Software's: sketch up

and AUTOCAD

Office Tools: Access, Powerpoint, Microsoft Word & Excel

EDUCATION

Higher National diploma (HND) in Electronic Electrical Engineering

JAN 2016 - DEC 2017 federal polytechnic auchi, Edo state

National diploma (OND) in Electronic Electrical Engineering

JAN 2013 - DEC 2014 federal polytechnic auchi, Edo state

West African Senior Secondary School Certificate (WASSCE)

SEPT 2008 - JUN 2012 Ehor grammer school, ehor,. Edo state.

CERTIFICATION

National Youth Service Corps (NYSC) Discharge Certificate

MARCH 2018 - MARCH 2019 Portharcourt Electric distribution company Rivers State

Hse level 1, 2, & 3

| APRIL 2019 Onshore and offshore safety institute.

EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

- > Machine and equipment electrical maintenance.
- Confirms electrical system and capacities during project execution.
- > Ensures project meet electrical and construction safety standard.
- Provide project estimate for project by calculating labor, material and related cost.
- Provide detail specification for electrical material and equipment to be purchased.
- Coordinate and train technician and other team project member as necessary.
- Negotiating and maintaining relationship with over 15 vendors across the country that led to significant cost savings.
- Prepared project schedules and drafted contract documents, developed Cost estimates and allocated resources for construction Projects.
- Resolved all issues at the project location quickly and effectively to avoid work delays.

CUSTOMER ENUMERATION & ASSET MAPPING

| JUNE 2018 - MARCH 2019

Port Harcourt Electricity Distribution Company Port Harcourt.

- Develop clear and concise reports that identify strategic information and provide recommendations for performance improvement.
- Work with senior leaders and internal business managers to execute key strategic projects and assist with solving day-today business issues
- Support the management and implementation of elements of the strategic asset management plan and overall organization roadmap.
- Provides advisory and support to facilitate the improvement of the assets in the assigned portfolio

Professional certificate program (HSE-PCP)

| DEC 2018

Jointly certified by national industrial safety council (FMLP)

level 3 certification in environmental risk management with practice

| DEC 2018 Safeguard safety and

FIRST AID AND CPR

| DEC 2018 Jointly certified by Saint John's ambulance

Fire prevention, protection and practical firefighting

| DEC 2018 Jointly certified by national fire prevention project (federal fire service)

REFERENCES

ENGR ATEMEA BRIGSS (DIRECTOR NELHOLDMAN NIG LTD) 08125880966

MRS ESTHER ASIKI BRIGSS (MD NELHOLDMAN NIG LTD) 08037127724

ENGR AKIMBOBOYE OLAWALE(NNPC) 08056817096

ENGR PETER ASEMOTA (NNPC) 08029582251

MRS OHIKHUAI HAUWA (ASS GENERAL MANAGER ECTS) 08034034538

ENGR SEUN FADARE (NIPP/NDPHC) 08055866141

Etc.

EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

ELECTRICAL IMPROVER

| MAY 2015 - JUN 2018 Absolute core engineering company.

- Directed and oversaw shop repairs on high/low voltage equipment's to ensure quality standards were adhered to
- Prepared reports at the conclusion of critical jobs for proper historical documentation; execute equipment maintenance strategies and perform other duties or
- Managed project budgets of over \$18,000 and achieved cost savings of about 20%.
- Supervised teams of over 50 electricians to successfully execute the entire scope of works which included cable pulling, tray installation, high level wiring of lights, small power and lighting, making off circuits in distribution boards, responded and provided technical assistance to electrical equipment problems in industrial, commercial and private homes, offices and facilities.
- Planned, designed and successfully executed Maintenance works of electrical instruments, equipment, facilities, components and systems at various locations across Nigeria.
- Executed several material procurement and delivery
- Performed several building designs wiring and installations for both domestic, commercial, industrial and private properties
- Installed and maintained office equipment
- Repaired private and office electrical appliances
- > Troubleshoot and resolved electrical faults from several clients

INDUSTRIAL TRAINING/INTERNSHIP

| APRIL 2015 - FEB 2016

NIGERIA PETROLEUM DEVELOPMENT COMPANY (NNPC subsidiary).

- > Supported project engineers in supervising and coordinating activities at four oil and gas drilling stations.
- Drafted and presented electrical drawings using AutoCAD.
- Prepared project schedules, developed bill of quantities, and created progress reports for ongoing projects.
- Monitored and recorded process parameters (pressure and temperatures) for the equipment and installations (Separators, gas scrubbers, Storage tanks) at the flow station.

NATIONAL INTEGRATED POWER PROJECT (NIPP/NDPHC).

| NOV 2014 - MARCH 2015

- Supported the operations and maintenance activities on 4 no's general electric gas fired simple cycle turbine 120MW and 15KVA brush generator(coupled).
- Worked on programmable logic controllers, G.E Speedtronic mark VI, Allen Bradly, Honeywell, Siemens etc.
- Worked on the ABB switchgears
- Worked on Hydraulic, pneumatic and electrical signal control systems.
- Worked on heat extortion fans, 415/230 electric motors in star-delta, 6.6kv cranking motors, pumps.
- Worked on Instrument transmitters and controllers (level/temperature/pressure).

EDO CITY TRANSPORT SERVICE COMPANY.

| NOV 2013 - FEB 2014

Four months' attachments 2013 (now working with them as an electrical contractor solving several electrical engineering issues that arise in the company bringing to the management the best and cost effective solutions).

PART-TIME ELECTRICAL TRAINEE/APPRENTICE

| JULY 2007 - JUNE 2015

Uyi electrical company, Edo state.

- Went through rigorous training for the period of 8 years and serves as my foundational knowledge of practical work in electrical engineering discipline.
- Learnt under the direct tutor of the Senior Electrical personnel how to manage an electrical contracting business.
- Carried out several material procurement and delivery
- carried out several building designs wiring and installations for both domestic, commercial, industrial and private properties
- Installed and maintained office equipment
- Repaired private and office electrical appliances
- > Troubleshoot and resolved electrical faults from several clients.